{
    "id": "4ac6757ffbf0459a9c3421d4cb6c86a4",
    "title": "Each vs. Every",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You have to change the sheets .......................... other day.",
            "description": "Every is used with expressions like other, few and numbers.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "696fbfde0fc74c25bdac3b7bf3c17deb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Buses leave .......................... ten minutes.",
            "description": "Every can be used before a plural noun in expressions that refer to intervals. ",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2cec50171104502944e32b3dcbace62"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ team in a cricket game has 11 players.",
            "description": "Each is used to talk about two or more things. Every is used to talk about three or more things.Ever",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "270b3cbe2ab14a4badf95cc26b362e57"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................... of them was given a present.",
            "description": "Every cannot be used before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01de38bbc25f47b98ab5f2f1939e475c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could understand ........................... word she said.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0808e48b17d7499087074e1fa2d7d652"
        },
        {
            "question": "The four students ........................... received a laptop.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "876e20ed046d44b5a7783c0ab6f62347"
        },
        {
            "question": "She kissed them ............................... on the forehead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c04e5fd341741abbf929108f382296a"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ............................ chance that we will win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e3225a09a75b41c3abdfcffc26e52dea"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ of them was asked to speak for a few minutes.",
            "description": "Every cannot be used before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d9f646ef92d496789e51e995a7b03c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit my grandparents .............................. now and then.",
            "description": "Every is used in expressions like every now and then.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "729f52b898ad491d97326fc31f940857"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have written to ................................ friend I have.",
            "description": "Either could be used here",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5aef1fc0e4a94dc5b1dbdc177f218cd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Almost ............................. child in cities receives school education.",
            "description": "Each cannot be used with expressions like almost, nearly, practically or without exception.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "807ec8e6e90b43889695cd08a6632291"
        }
    ]
}